onlineagency.com 2017-11-14

# Online Agency Privacy Policy

At LevelField.com, Inc. d/b/a OnlineAgency.com (hereinafter referred to as "Online Agency"), we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and visitors. We know you care about what happens to your personal information on the Internet, so we think it is important for you to understand our privacy practices with respect to that personal information when you visit our web site (the "Site") and use our services. We have created this privacy statement to explain what kind of information we collect from our customers, what we do with that information, and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

This privacy policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.

1\. **What kind of information does Online Agency collect from you?**

We offer on our web site various services to provide you with travel content, information, programs, promotions and packages, provide you with web tools to create and design your own travel web site, and/or host your web site for you (collectively referred to as the "Service"). ln order to provide you this Service as requested by you and to personalize this Service, we need to collect certain information about you. There are two types of information that we collect.

a. **Your Contact Information**

When you register for our Service, we ask you for information that personally identifies you, such as your legal name or business name, address, telephone number(s), email address, subscriber name or screen name, password used to access the Service, URL of your web site (if applicable), demographics, method of payment, and, if applicable, credit card number and billing address.

We may also ask you for additional personal information at various times such as when we run a promotion, hold a contest or conduct surveys. We may later request additional personal information from you in order to establish and maintain your account.

We do not knowingly allow anyone under the age of 18 to register with our Site or for our Service or to access those features that require registration.

b. **Your IP Address**

When you visit our Site or register for our Service, our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address (which is a number that lets our server know the "location" of your computer on the Internet). We use your IP address to (i) deliver our web pages to you upon request; (ii) tailor our Site and Service to your and other users' interests; (iii) help diagnose problems with our server; (iv) administer our Site in order to constantly improve the quality of our Service; (v) measure traffic within our Site; and (vi) prevent fraudulent use of the Service by others. We may also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from you and other users, and provide such information to third parties.

2\. **How does Online Agency use your information?**

The information we collect helps us to verify your identity, establish an account for you, offer you more personalized features, deliver the Service to you, and improve our Service and Site. If you give us your permission, we use your contact information from the registration form to send you information about us and about promotions and events offered by us or third parties who help us to bring the Service to you ("Alliance Partners"). You may select to opt-out of future unsolicited mailings by following the opt-out provision below. 

We also research your and other users' demographics and interests based on the information provided upon registration, in our server log files, or from surveys. We use personal demographic and profile data to tailor your experience in our Service and on our Site, create personalized content and promotions, and show you content that might interest you or that you preferred.

3\. **Does Online Agency share your information with other companies?**

We never sell, trade, rent, or share any of your personally identifiable information with third parties outside of Online Agency without your consent. However, we will pass on personal information about you only under the following circumstances:

We may pass on some of your personal contact information to our Alliance Partners, third party service providers and content suppliers, if we determine that such Alliance Partners, third party service providers and content suppliers need the information in order to provide you with the Service. They may also use your personal information for billing and market analysis purposes. Our Alliance Partners and content suppliers may not sell or share any of the personal information they receive from us, nor may they use it except to provide the Service (unless you specifically give them permission to do otherwise). Our Alliance Partners and content suppliers may have their own privacy policies which govern how they deal with any information you give to them directly.

Any credit card or financial information that you submit to us will be verified with certain third parties. The credit card or financial information is encrypted through the entire verification process.

In the future, we may offer you the option to attract visitors to your web site through participation in search engines, comparative shopping services, or similar distribution opportunities. When that happens, as part of the Service and other features on our Site, we will by necessity need to provide some of the information publicly available on your web site to third party search engines offering search services. We may also distribute information about your products and services, your web site address (URL), your contact information, and other personal information publicly available on your site to our search engine and various other comparative shopping and search services partners. We may also create a database of public available information about your or your business for our search partners with the express purpose of driving Internet user traffic to your web site, provided that such information is useful to the end users visiting your site. Your public information means information available to the public and end users visiting or browsing your site, and includes, but is not limited to, information about the products or services you offer through your site, your legal name, your operating hours, your business address, your URL, your business contact information, your email address, and other similar information. However, we will not disclose your billing and credit card information to these search partners.

We will provide your personal information when it is required to do so by a court, civil service process, or regulatory or law enforcement agency. In addition, you authorize us to disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other governmental officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe is necessary or appropriate.

From time to time we may also share anonymous demographic and profile data with our Alliance Partners, advertisers, and other third parties. This information is in the form of aggregate statistics, and will not include names, addresses, and other personally identifiable information.

By registering for an account to use our Service, you grant Online Agency your consent to provide your personal information as described above and to the extent necessary to deliver the Service to you. 

4\. **Does Online Agency use Cookies?**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that we store on your computer's hard drive while you visit or browse our web site. Like many sites on the Internet, we use cookies to identify you when you use our Service, to enable you to easily navigate our web site, and to personalize your experience when using our Service. We do not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information from your computer.

In order to use the Service, your web browser must be set to accept cookies. Most Web browsers are automatically set to accept cookies. The "help" section of your browser explains how to configure your computer to accept or reject cookies (but if you reject cookies, you will not be able to use the Online Agency Service).

Some of our Alliance Partners and other third parties (such as advertisers) may use cookies on our web site. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

5\. **How does Online Agency protect my personal information?**

At Online Agency, we take security very seriously. We have security measures in place to minimize the risk of loss, misuse, and alteration of your personal information, and unauthorized access to such information. When you register for our Service, we use secure server software (SSL) to encrypt the information you input before it is sent to us. We also use standard and customary security measures to protect any information you send through the Service (like firewalls, encryption, and a secure data center). Of course, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, we do not warrant that your information will be absolutely secure.

Also, your account information at Online Agency is password-protected so that only you have access to that personal information. Keep your password private and secure, and do not share your password with anyone. If you lose your password, we will issue you a new one. Online Agency will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited email or phone call.

6\. **What about the privacy policies of sites linking to our Site or to which Online Agency links?**

Although we take careful security measures to protect your personal information, we cannot control or be responsible for third party sites that are linked to or from our web site. Once you leave our server, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. That policy may be different from ours. Online Agency is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any site other than the Online Agency Site. We are not responsible for the content, or endorse the subject matter, of any advertisements (including without limitation rotating banners) on our Site, our Alliance Partners' sites, or the web sites of any other third parties. The existence of a link between the Online Agency Site and other third party sites does not imply an endorsement of those other sites.

7\. **How can you make changes to your personal information?**

You may update and/or correct your personal information at any time by logging into your account profile and making the changes, or by sending an email to support@onlineagency.com.

8\. **Can you opt out of receiving unsolicited communications from Online Agency?**

We offer you the opportunity to opt out of receiving unsolicited communications, promotions or other marketing materials from Online Agency at the time you sign up for the Service. You can also opt-in or opt-out of receiving these communications, promotions or marketing materials at any time by updating your account profile on our web site, or by sending an email to support@onlineagency.com. 

9\. **What constitutes your acceptance of this privacy policy?**

By using the Service or our web site, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of your information as described in this privacy policy. If we make any changes in the way we use your personal information, we will post the changes in an updated version of the privacy statement appearing on our web site. Be sure to check back periodically. Your continued use of our Service or web site after the effective date of any change to the privacy statement will be deemed to be your agreement to the modified terms.

10\. **How will you be notified in the event of material changes to Online Agency's privacy policy?**

If Online Agency makes any material change(s) to its privacy policy, we will send you an email, addressed to the email address you have provided to us for member related notifications, describing the change(s) and when such change(s) will become effective.

11\. **How can you contact Online Agency if you have questions or want to cancel your account?**

If you decide to cancel your Online Agency account, send an email to support@onlineagency.com.

If you have any other questions about Online Agency or suspect that this privacy statement has been violated, send an email to support@onlineagency.com. Or you can contact us via regular mail at this address:

Webmaster  
c/o LevelField.com, Inc.  
11675 Jollyville Rd, Suite 207 Austin, TX 78759
